<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PalisocShop</string>
    <string name="browse_header">Browse</string>
    <string name="rydel_racing_bikes">Rydel\'s Racing Bikes</string>
    <string name="browse">Browse</string>
    <string name="instruct_msg">Welcome to Mike\'s Mach Bikes! Browse through our catalog and order yourself a brand new bike, tailored and delivered, just for you</string>
    <string name="item1_name">Mach Bike 2020</string>
    <string name="item1_price">599.98</string>
    <string name="item1_description">54 Cm Light Aluminum Frame more light for your cycling.
        16 Speed Shifting system ensure you to brakes for safety at any speed.
        Double wall Aluminum Rims makes it more fashion.
        Due to bicycle are overweight products,if there are any damages caused during the shipping,please contact us directly for solve the problems.
        Bicycle Serials number at the bottom tube or head tube of frame, please find it and make a note ,if the bicycle was stolen, you can provide it to the police.
        This is sole signs that distinguishes the same serials products.If there any questions,please contact us directly for assistance.</string>
    <string name="item2_name">Acro 7200</string>
    <string name="item2_price">356.98</string>
    <string name="item2_description">21 Speed Shimano Shifting system ensure you to brakes for safety at any speed. Please rotate the fork 180 degree before assemble front wheel, make sure the front brake and the rear brake at same side of the bike.If the brake installed incorrect, the brake and gear system can not works. Dual Disc brake provided great stopping power. Bicycle Serials number at the bottom tube or head tube of frame, please find it and make a note ,if the bicycle was stolen, you can provide it to the police. This is sole signs that distinguishes the same serials products.If there any questions,please contact us directly for assistance. Due to bicycle are overweight products,if there are any damages caused during the shipping,please contact us directly for solve the problems.</string>
    <string name="quantity">Quantity:</string>
    <string name="initial_quantity">0</string>
    <string name="add_button">Button</string>
    <string name="remove_button">Button</string>
</resources>
